Kim Soo-hyun - Kim Ji-won
Park Sung-hoon - Kwak Dong-yeon - Lee Joo-bin
Kim Gab-soo - Lee Mi-sook
Jung Jin-young - Na Young-hee
Jeon Bae-soo - Hwang Young-hee
Kim Jung-nan - Kim Joo-ryoung
Jang Yoon-ju - Kim Do-hyun
Screenwriter: Park Ji-eun
Directors: Jang Young-woo - Kim Hee-won
Queen of Tears
Episode 13
This is our home. Come on in.
Okay. This is my secret room.
When I open this handle and press this button...
Okay. What do you think?
It's empty.
Look here.
It seems something has been moved.
The marks look fresh.
Gosh, my dear father.
He must've secretly stashed it here,
but I guess that wench got to it again.
He didn't even tell his own
children about this secret room.
Did you send him off well?
It was you, wasn't it? You killed our father.
- Why would I?
- Because you didn't need him...
after taking his money.
Where is it?
I don't know what you're saying.
Your father is dead,
and you still want his money.
- Your poor father.
- Cut the nonsense.
Leave this home right now.
You have no right to be here anymore.
I'm a legal resident here.
If you want to kick me out,
the court needs to order it first.
Aren't you aware of this, Attorney Baek?
Is this true? We can't just kick her out?
There's a procedure, but you'll have to leave.
We'll see about that.
We're moving back in.
- Do you still want to stay?
- Why not?
We've been living together for over 20 years.
You said we were family.
- But...
- Suit yourself.
We'll be back soon.
Let's see if you can bear it.
Hae-in.
Grandfather?
I would've loved to speak to you...
in person,
but still,
I'm glad I can talk to you like this.
Thank you.
I briefly come to my senses every now and then,
like a basement that receives limited sunlight,
but there's not much I can do.
I don't remember much, either.
I'm just full of regrets.
I've been a money-grubber all my life.
I did everything in my power...
to keep the money I gathered.
I wasted most of my years doing that.
What am I left with?
I'd like you all to know that I regret...
the life I led.
Former Chairman Hong Man-dae
I hope you live differently.
I truly hope...
you won't look back in futility...
at the end of the road.
Dad...
I love you all,
and...
I'm sorry.
You need to eat, even if you're not hungry.
Do you want to go inside the car if you're cold?
It's okay.
This feels...
very strange.
It feels like I'm doing a rehearsal.
A rehearsal?
A death rehearsal.
I didn't know...
a funeral was so complex.
They dig a hole in the ground, place the coffin,
have some rice soup in a tent,
and mourn by the grave.
Then when it's time,
they'll all go home,
and I'll be all by myself.
You know the three months I've been given...
have already passed.
I could even die tonight,
but my family would have
to mourn again if I died.
That wouldn't...
look good for our family, right?
Was that...
what you've been worrying about?
That your family would mourn again?
No.
I kept thinking I wanted to live.
It's sunny.
The clouds look pretty,
and the birds are chirping.
This world is annoyingly beautiful,
so of course I want to live.
Checking ID
Please Wait
How did you find it?
Dreamland Theme Park
Okay. This is my secret room.
When I open this handle and press this button...
Thank you.
I told you.
I loved you in my own way.
This money will keep you safe.
His daughter is sick,
and now he lost his father.
Mr. Hong must be devastated.
Right,
but you can say things are
looking up for his family...
after the chairman passed away.
- Really?
- Gosh.
Hear me out.
Look.
Chairman Hong had entrusted 21% of his shares...
to that woman, Moh Seul-hee,
but now that he's passed away,
his family received it.
Yoon Eun-sung's total shares were 59.1%,
but now it's plummeted to 38.1%.
Once our in-laws get
hold of their frozen shares,
they'll have 34.7% in total.
Then the gap will be 3.4%.
- That's quite neck-and-neck.
- Right.
How do you know this so well?
- I'm a club member.
- What club?
The Queens Minor Stockholders' Club.
We're waiting for the management
feud results with bated breath.
What for?
I know I'm being calculating,
but what do you think...
- will happen to Hyun-woo?
- What do you mean?
Let's be honest. He's been doing...
his utmost best to help them after everything.
Perhaps they'll thank him in some way.
Maybe they'll give him some shares
or appoint him as a CEO later on.
I don't ask for much,
but could you do me this one favor?
Sure.
What is it?
If someone asks you who your father is,
please don't tell them it's me.
Gosh.
Why not?
Why not? Hey, wait for me.
Thank you for everything.
Gosh, don't mention it.
Things will look up once you return to Seoul.
Do you think so?
You see...
These persimmons...
used to be very bitter,
but there's a way to turn
this awfully bitter fruit...
- into a sweet one.
- How?
It's by soaking them.
You pour some soju on top,
wrap the bodies, then let
them sit for some time.
Then they become sweet.
Here. Try it.
It's sweet.
Life can be bitter, just like these persimmons.
Life is tough as it is,
so imagine pouring some bitter soju on top.
Gosh, it'd be utterly unbearable,
but if you endure it,
life will become sweet again,
and that'll motivate you to stay strong.
Don't you think so?
Right.
Hey, come and have a drink with us.
Sure.
International Call
I got a call from Germany. Excuse me.
Does that mean she can get surgery?
Yes.
Thank God.
Her case was a difficult one,
since they couldn't open up her brain,
but they can destroy the tumor cells...
using high-intensity ultrasound.
They had a successful case recently, too.
Good. Things are looking up now.
Thanks, Hyun-woo. Does Hae-in know?
- I should tell her.
- However,
there's a problem.
Goodness, Hae-in. This feels like a dream.
Gosh, this must be a gift...
from Father.
Is it true?
- Can she receive surgery?
- Yes.
I'm so happy for you.
Goodness.
I'm so grateful.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Sweetie.
How did they reach you? Via email? Phone?
Was it a video call?
They called me.
A phone call?
You don't think they were scammers, do you?
No, they weren't.
Okay. Good night.
By the way, are you sure the surgery
works in rare cases like mine?
Yes.
I'm sure.
I see.
And the date?
Tell them I can go right away.
I did.
Good, then.
Are you saying...
this surgery...
will save my life?
Does Hae-in know?
I should tell her.
However,
there's a problem.
A part of the hippocampus will be damaged...
- during the process.
- And?
It's highly likely...
that she'll lose her long-term memory.
Hold on.
What are you saying?
She could lose all her memory...
from before the surgery.
But this is our only choice...
if we want her...
to live.
Her WBC isn't going up quickly,
so she can't receive the clinical test.
We really have no time now.
She might refuse the surgery...
if she hears about the side effects.
But what if...
she runs out of time?
Hyun-woo.
Keep this a secret.
Why don't you take her to Germany
first, then persuade her there?
I beg you.
She needs the surgery to live.
Will I be able to live then?
What is it?
Yes, you will.
Don't worry.
All right.
Night.
Hae-in.
It's okay.
I'm fine. I really am.
It's just been ages since I felt fine.
These are tears of joy.
Yes, I know.
It feels like...
I woke up from a long nightmare.
You're okay now.
Let's go to bed.
Hae-in
Hyun-woo
You don't have to go to work today, right?
Right.
Then let's hang out.
Okay, let's do that.
Gurang-ri Station
Ticket Office
Two people.
All right.
- Okay, good.
- What?
Other than our honeymoon,
isn't this our first trip?
You're right.
I've been too much of a workaholic.
Let's go on many trips after I receive surgery.
Promise.
Okay.
Listen.
I want everything to be
smooth before I receive surgery.
You know I only drink extracted
juice for the same reason, right?
I do. What's on your mind?
I wasn't planning on hiding them,
but there are three things I kept from you.
Three?
I'll come clean before I go.
I'll tell you one for today.
Sure. What is it?
You said...
you found this MP3 player.
I did.
It's mine.
- What?
- Do you see this "H"?
It stands for "Hae-in."
I'd lost it in our schoolyard
before going abroad for my studies,
and look where it is now.
That can't be.
It sure can.
I don't believe it.
Something unbelievable happened to us.
It may not mean much to you,
since I was just a nobody in your life.
No, you're wrong.
Listen. I actually...
Don't be afraid.
I'm not scolding you. Why?
Because I'm not my old self.
I'll be reborn soon.
I'm going to be optimistic,
and only see the good in life.
Really?
Yes.
This MP3 player is a
living witness to our history,
so I'm only going to
focus on that positive point.
That's good.
Eun-sung told me...
how he'd saved me in the past,
and made it seem like we were fated.
What? Fated?
Gosh.
Has he gone crazy or what? How dare he say that?
So what? We have our own movie-like story.
When I saw you at the schoolyard,
I thought, "Does this
handsome kid go to my school?"
"I can't believe I'm leaving."
"I feel terrible."
That's what I thought.
Black slip-ons.
You were wearing...
black slip-ons.
You had white socks...
and very fair skin,
and your hair was in a high ponytail.
I did wear ponytails often back then.
The moment I saw you, I thought,
"I found her."
"My dream girl."
I looked everywhere for you,
starting the next day.
I didn't have a chance to look at your name tag.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You were like Cinderella.
You'd only left behind your MP3 player.
It drove me crazy,
but look at us now.
We crossed paths again, got married...
We did get divorced, but still.
This is what you call true fate.
All right.
Since I'm your dream woman,
and this is fate...
From now on...
I didn't know...
that phrase was this beautiful.
I'm getting teary-eyed.
I thought I wouldn't be a part of your future,
but now we have a future together.
Speaking of which,
I'll withdraw our divorce as you asked.
What's with that face?
Don't take it back.
I run a department store.
I hate customers who return
things and demand a refund.
You can't take this back,
even if you wake up one day...
and dislike me.
A change of mind isn't a valid
reason to get a refund. That's a given.
Even if we get...
into huge fights,
and you're sick of me...
Even if you claim you don't
remember making this promise,
there's no taking back.
I'll still be with you.
All right. Fine. Do that,
so stop talking.
I love it the most...
when I can just focus on your heartbeat.
I did some calculations.
5% would be $45 million,
but I'll just ask for $40 million.
I even have a car waiting
outside in case it's cash.
- A big one.
- Are you a creditor?
I may sound rude for saying this,
but perhaps our history
made me into who I am today.
I was betrayed several
times after doing all the work.
Check.
Ko Jeong-ja
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten...
I respect you, ma'am.
A gorgeous face, a silver
tongue, and alluring charisma.
It's rare for one to have them all.
I want to live wisely like you.
- The payment is suspended.
- Sorry?
You can only spend that money when I let you.
Ma'am.
Our history made you into who you are today?
Likewise. I was betrayed several times.
- Look.
- I'll lift the suspension...
once I'm content with your
work. Then you can take it.
Goodness.
You sure are wise.
Mom!
What's all this? It's not
even kimchi-making season!
Hae-in's family is leaving,
but I have nothing to give.
I'll give them some pear extract and kimchi.
This isn't little at all.
I thought I could share with our neighbors...
and the elderly.
You can't do this alone.
Then get some gloves and help out.
Well, I need these hands to make a living.
Let me help.
- Should I slice the radish?
- That'd be great.
Gosh, she's so fast.
She knows how to chop.
Her chopping skills were out of this world.
- And she has guts.
- Why?
Hey.
Do you think I'll take you back if you do this?
I don't expect you to.
I'm going to leave once I'm done here.
Don't worry, Mother.
Yet you still call me that.
Are you teasing me? Don't call me that.
But I'd like to.
What?
You're the first person I ever called "Mother,"
so please let me do that.
- Here you go.
- Hey.
- Are you done?
- Anything else?
That's enough.
I'll chop the green onions.
Unbelievable.
- I kind of like her.
- Why?
I like how she's not intimidated
and speaks her mind...
in front of her mother-in-law.
Hae-in.
Come sit. They all heard...
about your surgery and were happy for you.
I'm so happy for you.
- I'm glad.
- It all worked out.
Thank you.
By the way,
what were you doing?
Right. Have you done this before?
Dyeing your nails with balsam?
- No.
- Legend has it that, if your nails...
are still colored by the first snow,
your first love will come true.
That's why Bang-sil here always
dyes hers in the fall, not summer.
How romantic.
Actually, I'd say she has an ulterior motive.
I wouldn't say it's an ulterior motive.
He happens to be divorced.
- Hey.
- I didn't feel like this before,
but we've been running
into each other often lately,
so my feelings...
Shut that mouth of yours.
- That's enough.
- Stop.
- Shut it.
- Sorry.
I guess I was too blunt. I hope
you're not offended, Ms. Hong.
- Why would I be?
- You see,
Hyun-woo used to flirt a lot with me...
at church back when he was in high school.
When did he ever do that?
Didn't you know?
They used to hand out snacks at church,
and he'd always give me more than one...
in front of everyone.
That's because you always
ate other kids' snacks.
Hae-in, please don't misunderstand.
Don't talk such nonsense, Bang-sil.
Until the first snow, was it?
- Check this out.
- Balsam?
It's not that simple.
- Then?
- It signifies my excitement, hope,
and anticipation for the first
snow I thought I'd never see.
I didn't think I'd ever see winter again,
let alone the first snow,
but it's possible now.
Of course.
It'll come true if the
color still remains by then.
- What will come true?
- My first love.
By "first love,"
do you mean that guy on
the bus or taxi from before?
You're happy to watch them from afar.
You can't stop thinking about them.
You take a detour just to see them once more.
You were happy to watch him from afar.
You couldn't stop thinking about him,
and you took a detour just to see him once more.
That jerk?
Why are you cursing him?
Fine.
- That guy?
- Yes.
I hope it'll snow sooner...
this year.
Hae-in, you even took my ring back.
Your first love shouldn't come true,
or it'll really complicate things.
Are you listening?
Hae-in.
- Michael met with Hong Beom-seok?
- Yes, as the CEO of Ever H.
I guess the eldest son wants to
return, now that his father is dead.
Ever H recently appeared...
on the stockholder's list as
a non-institutional investor.
He must've been gathering
stocks ever since they plummeted.
He's been asking the anchor
limited partners for my spot.
He can try, but you'll be
safe with what I've given you.
As you said,
we founded paper companies
in Hong Kong and Switzerland,
and opened up an IEBC business account.
You're the only one who can manage it.
- What'll your first transaction be?
- Make it 2.1% in careful discretion.
- Yes, sir.
- He took the bait.
He's finally using the secret fund.
He's probably worried that
my uncle might take his spot.
Is Mr. Hong still in New York?
Yes, he's still meeting
with the limited partners.
Keep Eun-sung in the loop,
so he'll feel anxious and use
the secret fund to buy stocks.
- Yes, sir.
- Once we have concrete proof,
we can charge him for embezzlement,
malpractice, and violating...
foreign-exchange transaction laws.
By the way,
about that guy, Pyeon Seong-uk...
Isn't he the land broker who kidnapped you?
Yes, he'd agreed to hand over...
the double contract and
information on Director Jo,
and he never showed up, and I can't reach him.
He hasn't been spending any money
or using his phone for over a week now.
Maybe he stowed away.
Gosh!
A man, presumably in his forties,
was found dead last night...
near the Sambang Reservoir in Yeongjin-gun,
Gyeonggi Province.
He'd been stabbed with a weapon,
and his identity remains unknown
due to severe decomposition...
How could this be mine,
but not mine at the same time?
Ms. Kim!
The amazing Grace is here!
Gosh, why is she back?
What are you doing?
Can't you see? I'm making dried persimmons.
Goodness.
Your hands have gotten rough.
Look at those dark circles.
All the freckles I worked
hard to erase are back.
You'll be making a comeback soon.
It's a battlefield there.
Everyone will take sides between Ms. Moh,
that sly fox, and you.
What's the best way to intimidate your opponent?
With your face, of course. Lie down right now.
You need to look tight and radiant.
I've never done this before. It tickles.
Don't smile, or you'll get wrinkles.
Keep these words in mind.
Whitening, resilience, recovery, and comeback.
The best way to make a comeback
is through recovery and resilience.
Don't worry. Everything
will return to its place.
We'll return to Queens,
and Hae-in will get surgery
and become healthy again.
Is she getting surgery?
I thought surgery wasn't an option.
We found a hospital that could do it.
She'll be leaving for Germany soon.
Really?
I'm so glad.
- Right?
Hello, I wanted to see you.
- See me?
- Yes.
- I have something for you,
- What is it?
...but I didn't think I'd
run into you, so it's at home.
Shall we meet tonight?
- At night?
- Yes.
Sure, then.
Why does he want to meet at this hour?
He's such a go-getter.
He's dangerous.
You were already here.
Yes.
- So I...
- Let me go first.
Okay. I'm listening.
I'll be leaving...
tomorrow,
and I don't know when I'll ever return.
I heard you were leaving, so...
I know what you want to say.
I caught onto it...
from the mulberry incident,
- but no.
- Sorry?
What do you...?
I have...
a lot on my plate.
Not only do I have movable assets,
real estate, stocks, and bonds,
but I also have three ex-husbands.
I had no idea.
Right?
Anyway,
I'm complicated,
and carry many burdens,
so I can't...
accept it.
I hope you still will.
What is this?
Did you write a letter?
You really shouldn't...
Condolences
Kim Yeong-song
It's condolence money.
I heard about your father.
I don't need this.
- I should go.
- No, wait.
Come on. This isn't right.
This isn't for you.
It's for your father.
Even the wealthiest start off
with no money in the afterlife.
It's not much, but I'm sure...
he'll be able to enjoy some
rice soup and drinks tonight...
with his friends.
He'll be enjoying good food,
and having a great time with his friends,
so don't be too sad.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
What do you mean?
You want to stay here?
I'm dumbfounded.
It's temporary, just until
we find a place in Seoul.
Your mother doesn't understand
why you need to find a place.
I've had two training wheels
throughout my whole life.
One was you,
and the other one was you.
What are you saying?
But now...
I want to remove them and
stand on my own two feet.
Don't be ridiculous.
Hey, did you persuade him?
- Did you urge him again?
- Honey, be quiet.
Don't say a thing.
Plead the Fifth.
You're forbidden from speaking to her directly.
- If you want, speak to our attorney.
- What?
- Please do that, Hyun-woo.
- Sorry, but I refuse.
Hey, you can take care
of your own family issues.
Since we're on this topic,
let me say something too.
I'm not going home, either.
You too?
We're moving into his studio apartment in Seoul.
We'll be leaving for Germany soon,
and it's closer to the airport.
No, it's actually farther from there.
Best of all, it's newly
built and fully furnished.
It has everything we need in that small area,
but back home,
we need to take the
elevator to reach the kitchen.
It just takes way too long.
Hey, your excuses are lengthier.
You just want some alone time.
Yes, ma'am.
I'd like to spend some time with her alone.
Please let us do that.
Sure, if that's more comfortable for you.
Sure, you can do that.
Let me know if you need anything.
Gosh.
Is this what discrimination feels like?
This is my first time experiencing it.
It's something new, though.
They're packing up and returning tomorrow.
You should be ready for them.
I also met with Da-hye.
What is this?
Why did you return?
Don't let Ms. Moh know.
You idiot.
She was the one who told me you were here.
Seriously?
She knows how you came here...
in a taxi with the golden
Buddha in the middle of the night.
Her men are watching you,
so tell me, why are you here?
Is it guilt or a grudge?
What grudge could I have?
It's my conscience.
I didn't know you had one.
Me neither.
He was the first person to love
me for who I was, and I felt bad.
Oh, my.
Unbelievable.
He grew on her.
I'm sure you know those
feelings can't be stopped.
How dare she betray me
after all I've done for her?
This is exactly why you shouldn't trust people.
About Hae-in...
She might be able to save herself.
She's getting surgery.
Hyun-woo looked everywhere for help,
and they finally found a hospital that can help.
They're leaving for Germany next week.
You startled me.
Find out which hospital and what
kind of surgery she's receiving.
What are you doing?
Nothing much.
I can see many stars.
I even saw a shooting star recently.
Really?
I dreamed of one when I was pregnant with you.
I always wanted a pretty daughter.
I was ecstatic...
after having that dream.
I don't know which attitude to take.
We were like cats and dogs for over 20 years,
so I feel awkward to suddenly
act so affectionate toward you,
but deep down,
I feel so guilty...
and regretful.
I want to treat you well.
This is good enough.
Is it?
I'd feel awkward, too, if you
suddenly changed your ways.
We'll have a lot of time,
so let's take it slowly.
This'll do for now.
All right.
Once you return from Germany, we
can gradually warm up to each other.
I didn't know it was this suffocating...
to act as a mediator.
Right. They say it's just as
stressful as joining the military.
We need to move out of the
place if I want to protect Da-hye...
from my mom.
Gosh. What's taking them so long?
Mom, Dad.
I packed your stuff.
Really? Okay.
You'll run into traffic soon,
so you should go now. Hurry.
I'm sorry for all the inconvenience,
but I feel the most guilty
about leaving him behind.
It feels like leaving...
a bag of trash behind after a trip.
- Father...
- Gosh, don't worry,
and why are you in a hurry?
Have lunch with us.
Should we?
No! Our home has been
empty for over a month now.
There's a lot to take care of.
- I was going to make kimchi pancakes.
- It's okay.
Kimchi pancakes?
How about some crispy kimchi
pancakes and delicious makgeolli?
That's ridiculous. He needs to drive.
I can drive instead.
Better yet, you can leave tomorrow.
- You should.
- We could.
Do you know how beautiful it is...
to know when to leave?
Must I know that?
We'll get going now.
We don't want to run into traffic.
Okay, you should go before then.
Thank you for everything. Goodbye.
Good luck with the surgery.
Hae-in.
Let's meet again.
Hyun-woo.
I trust you.
Don't worry.
Here.
Your mom made some kimchi and pear extract.
Carry it for him.
Should I? Give it to me.
Goodbye.
Mom, your handbag...
You're the bachelor on the 11th floor.
- Hello.
- Hi.
He's not a bachelor.
I'm his wife.
Didn't you say...
you were living here by yourself?
Did you get married recently?
- Yes.
- Goodness!
You're newlyweds!
You must be so happy.
Yes, we are.
It's official that we're newlyweds now.
Why is it official?
Because of that lady.
A woman like her will tell everyone
in this building about us by tomorrow.
"The bachelor on the 11th
floor married a gorgeous woman."
Okay. So?
We should act like newlyweds, then.
How?
Normally, newlyweds in love...
are always touching each other somehow.
It could be their hands, feet,
or shoulders.
Anything.
They stick by each other,
and spend their daily lives together.
We're bound to run into hardships again one day.
I'm nervous. Did you smile?
Then we can pull out these happy memories,
like they're candies in a candy jar,
and endure those moments.
That's why we need to gather...
as many good memories as possible right now.
That looks tasty.
I'm going to start focusing
more on collecting...
happy memories than stocks or money.
The most important thing for me now...
is filling up my candy jar.
Why did you come here so often?
Is baseball that fun?
That's not why.
All I need to focus on is hitting the ball.
That's what I liked.
Does that...
make you feel better?
Well... It was nice to focus on one
thing when things were complicated.
I just need to concentrate...
on what's the most important.
What is that...
right now?
Saving you, of course.
That's all that matters.
I'll only focus on that.
Soo-cheol is staying in Yongdu-ri for some time.
Hae-in decided to stay with Hyun-woo, too.
Only the vice chairman
and his wife are returning.
The vice chairman?
I'm sorry,
but now that they have their shares,
wouldn't he want to take back his position?
Says who?
They'll regret coming back here.
I was meaning to see you.
Can we talk?
I heard Hae-in is getting surgery in Germany.
Don't be so alarmed.
I'm just happy for her.
Really?
Of course.
I have feelings for her, so
it's natural for me to be happy...
that she can live.
I heard you're going with her.
Please take care of her.
Okay.
May I leave now?
I found out...
that the surgery has a side effect.
Does she know?
Of course not.
Given her personality, she'd refuse
to get the surgery if she knew,
so she probably doesn't know.
What are you getting at?
Make sure you keep that secret,
so she gets the surgery.
I told you.
I want her to live.
Remove all their belongings,
and give Mr. Baek back what's his.
You wanted to come here as
a customer instead of the CEO,
so I even took leave.
Yes, I'm here as a customer.
- What'll you buy?
- I'm just looking.
Didn't you hate those who didn't buy anything?
Is this a sauna?
Why are they chatting and
not spending any money here?
- Get rid of the chairs.
- Mom!
Why are they running around?
They should do that at an amusement park.
That's why we got rid of all the rest zones.
Fine.
I'll spend some money, then.
Do you want anything?
- What do you need?
- Lip balm.
My lips are dry.
Why am I so tired after shopping?
Are you tired?
That's not good.
Let's rest somewhere.
No.
This is good.
The layout is incredible.
There's no time to rest.
We shopped for lip balm and bought cream, too.
We shopped for some knitwear
and bought a coat, too.
We didn't even plan on buying a
muffler or gloves, but we got them too,
and now the smell of perfume is attracting us.
That was your strategy.
You wanted to keep the customers busy.
That's why you set up so many pop-up stores.
When I'm reinstated,
I'm going to get rid of them.
- Why?
- It's tiring.
I feel stupid for spending money.
I feel duped.
Would you want to come back here?
I'll get rid of them and
set up chairs once again.
Expensive and comfortable ones.
I'll renovate the square on
the first floor and hold concerts.
There'll be an area where kids can run around,
What?
...and a place for couples.
The parents can bring...
their kids here when it's cold or hot outside.
It'd be nice.
I'll give them happiness.
Seriously?
Seriously.
You'd better not take
that back after the surgery.
Why would I?
I saw it in the movies.
Your personality can change,
or you can lose your memory,
after brain surgery.
You're wrong. I just simply want
to become a slightly better person,
to reciprocate...
for being able to live longer.
Mother.
Isn't that your wife?
Hello, Mother.
Sweetie, what's that modest look in your eyes?
You're making me anxious.
- Mother...
- I can't fix him.
You can't return him!
I'm sorry.
I tried to keep our promise,
but I'm afraid it's time.
Fine.
Let me hear your reason.
- Tell her.
- Me?
Right.
I lied to you about attending a funeral
and spent the night gaming with friends.
No? It's not that, Mom.
Right.
Did you find my game console?
It's secondhand. It's cheap.
You even bought a game console?
Can't you just tell me what it is?
Mother, Hyeon-tae spent our
savings on buying stocks.
He lost half of it.
Hey!
He even invested in cryptocurrency.
It's minus 90% now.
You lunatic.
I'm sorry.
Hyeon-suk.
I don't know what to say.
Return him to me, and I'll get rid of him.
You should go on your way...
- while you still have time.
- Mom...
Still,
I'll text you when I make kimchi,
so make sure you come.
Even I think someone as wise and
pretty as you is out of his league.
I'm truly sorry, Hyeon-suk.
Mother...
You need to come to your senses!
Honey, I...
Let me go!
Honey, I think I'll be getting some money!
Hae-in had bought a building,
but didn't have time to look at it.
This must be it.
Yes. I cleaned and swept
the building twice a day,
waxed and washed all the signs,
and disinfected the septic tanks.
I'm also going to paint the building soon.
Yes.
There's a good floating population
and visibility due to the two-lane road.
It'd be easy to get rent.
Right.
It's not bad at all,
but why do you ask?
Do you plan on selling it?
I spoke with Hae-in.
We'd like to gift the building to you.
What did you say?
Our tax accountant will
contact you once we go to Seoul,
and tell you what documents to prepare.
But still,
it's an entire building.
It's a thank-you gift.
Gosh, it's a huge gift.
My parents will become building owners!
Will you still return me?
Honey.
- You shouldn't be here.
- What?
Go to the building owners.
Hurry.
I'm thinking about renovating the first floor...
and setting up a fitness center.
Hey, just focus on your current gym.
Mom, I've been wanting
to relocate my hair salon.
The first floor would be perfect.
Don't get involved. I was the
one who cleaned and swept...
I removed all the stickers on the
stairs, and you have the third floor.
- Hyeon-tae.
- Yes, Mom?
Get rid of the gym as soon as you can.
Mom, that's a harsh joke.
It's not a joke. You haven't been paying rent.
Come on, Mom.
- Dad.
- Son.
Yes?
This is when a contract becomes useful.
"If a tenant fails to pay
rent two times or more,"
"the contract can be terminated."
- Do you want to see?
- So what?
- Are you kicking me out?
- No.
I'm telling you to pay up.
Pay on the tenth of every month.
Dad.
What about me?
The first floor costs a thousand.
Move in if you can manage it.
That's more expensive than my current rent.
Our building has a better location.
Anyway, we look forward...
to this new tension between us,
thanks to this building.
We're very excited.
Come on, Dad.
We don't need tension in this family.
I do!
There were times when I felt
like you were impudent.
This building will prove...
your loyalty to us.
- You're wrong.
- What?
I just want to receive rent.
Did you now?
You should've told me.
Anyway...
- Our Dubong Building...
- What?
- What is that?
- Du-gwan and Bong-ae's building.
How tacky.
We expect you to pay rent religiously,
despite being our children.
Keep that in mind.
It's only October, but
they're preparing for Christmas.
It was your order.
Mine?
Are you going to relax because Chuseok is over?
Christmas is upcoming. Winter is coming.
We should liven up the mood...
so they'll want to buy winter jackets.
We shouldn't wait until the other stores begin.
We need to prepare in advance
and start the Christmas sale...
right after Halloween.
- Are they testing the lights?
- Yes.
The installation and marketing
teams have been busy today.
Am I hallucinating...
the snow?
I see it too,
but isn't this just a rehearsal?
One minute.
It's snowing in the fall.
You wanted to see snow sooner.
Your wish came true.
You're right.
Things are looking up.
All my wishes are coming true.
I think my first love will come true, too.
Well...
I don't think that's what this snow is for.
Why not?
I'll bet it'll come true.
Who is he,
that you're so bent on it?
I wasn't ever going to tell you,
in case you'd become too arrogant,
but here's my second secret.
- What is it?
- Was it bus number 372?
- What do you mean?
- The bus you took...
back home after work.
Right. Yes.
You're right.
You always sat in the back next to the window.
Yes, I did. How did you know that?
How do you think I know?
I followed your bus home,
and crossed the Han River numerous times...
despite all the traffic.
It took an hour and a half.
Why?
That bus I told you about was bus number 372,
and the guy is you.
Okay.
How did you even get into SNU?
What?
So it's me?
Me? I was the guy on the bus?
Yes, it was you.
How lovey-dovey.
By the way, why did the
installation team sprinkle snow?
It was Director Baek's request.
Sir, please test the
snowmaker during the rehearsal.
I don't think that's necessary.
The legal team needs to prepare themselves.
You know it'd be an issue if
a customer slipped and fell.
I need to determine how slippery it'll get.
Sure, if you must.
I'd like big snowflakes, if possible.
Yes, sir. Understood.
- Thank you, sir.
- No problem.
I sense love in the air.
Right?
Divorce then remarriage.
It's possible?
Was it really me?
Was I your first love?
They must've already left.
I wonder when they'll arrive.
It'll take some time.
My morning prayers were answered.
Hae-in will get better after the surgery,
and be happy with Hyun-woo.
You see...
There's a problem.
What problem?
After having surgery...
Goodness.
She might lose her memory.
What do you mean?
That could be a side effect,
but what choice do we have?
She needs to live.
We had no choice.
I asked Hyun-woo to keep it a secret.
That was...
wise of you.
She has a terrible personality,
since she takes after me,
so she might've refused to get the surgery,
but...
Still...
What'll we do about our poor baby?
Poor baby...
Are you okay?
Of course I am.
Don't worry.
Are you going to Frankfurt?
Yes.
Body Found Near Sambang Reservoir
Identified as Land Broker, Mr. Pyeon
What's the third one?
What do you mean?
You had three secrets to
tell me before the surgery.
You only told me two so far.
That?
The third one is...
- Yeong-suk.
- Yeong-suk?
- The raccoon on the rooftop?
- Yes.
I never got to see her.
Seriously,
not even once.
- What about her?
- I made it up.
How could a raccoon live there?
Did you really believe that?
Wow.
You duped me for four years.
I called out her name every time I was up there.
You fool.
Is this it?
Hae-in.
What is it?
There's something...
I didn't tell you too.
What is it?
What?
Is something wrong?
Can't they operate...
on me?
No, that's not it.
It's...
highly likely...
that you'll lose your memory after the surgery.
What do you mean?
What memory?
Probably...
all of it.
You'll forget...
everyone, the places you've been,
and all the experiences you've had.
Even still, this is...
your only chance...
to live.
So...
you're telling me...
to make a decision?
I'll lose my memory if
I get it and die if I don't.
Are you telling me to pick the lesser evil?
No.
Then what?
Forget it.
I'll pretend this was all a good dream.
Let me go. I said, let go.
Don't make a choice.
Don't think.
Just listen to me.
Just live.
Do that.
Please...
live.
Okay?
Hi, Hae-in.
I'm Baek Hyun-woo.
I'm your husband.
You must be confused and scared.
Me too.
You don't remember anything,
and a stranger is claiming to be your husband.
You must be so confused.
But...
this is good news.
You...
You were very sick,
but you're better now.
You must be curious about what
kind of person you used to be.
It must be upsetting...
that you can't remember,
but don't worry,
because I...
I remember everything.
I'll tell you everything...
I know.
I shouldn't cry.
This will be the first time...
you see my face,
and let me warn you.
Even if I'm not your ideal type,
I'm sorry, but I can't break up with you,
because we agreed...
not to part ways just because...
of a change of mind.
Even if you don't like me,
no matter what happens...
Even if...
you forget...
the promise we made,
I promised...
to always...
stick with you.
Let's welcome the first snow,
stick by each other,
and spend our daily lives together.
Let's fill up...
that empty candy jar...
of yours.
We can do it,
because it was fate that brought us together.
I love...
I love you, Hae-in.
I've always loved you,
and will continue to.
Queen of Tears
I still remember...
the smell,
the moon, and the wind of that day.
Don't pray...
about dying.
That so-called family of yours will get hurt.
Da-hye...
I lived as myself,
and I'll die as such...
I won't let that happen.
That's how he found that hospital.
I'll help you.
Don't do this to me.
Don't make me want to live.
Hae-in!